[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the study of knowledge?", "correct_answer": "epistimology", "incorrect_answers": ["rheology", "pulicology", "dialitology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country is the biggest contributor to the European Union budget?", "correct_answer": "Germany", "incorrect_answers": ["UK", "Italy", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did Dax Shepard play in the movie Cheaper by the Dozen?", "correct_answer": "Camera Crew Member", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Baker", "Jake Baker", "Reporter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before the car accident in Fight Club, Tyler Durden asks his passengers what they wish they would have done before they died. Stephs answers is Paint a self-portrait.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country was the goldfish first domesticated?", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Egypt", "Japan", "India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what firm does Chris get an internship in the drama movie The Pursuit of Happyness?", "correct_answer": "Dean Witter", "incorrect_answers": ["Merrill Lunch", "Goldman Sachs", "Smith Barney"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After having the huge row after the family meal what does Gary purchase on the 2006 film The Break-Up?", "correct_answer": "Pool Table", "incorrect_answers": ["Art Museum", "Car", "Strip Club"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the approximate weight standard, that a Yorkshire Terrier show dog cannot go over?", "correct_answer": "No standard", "incorrect_answers": ["7 lbs", "10 lbs", "2 lbs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the first known blondes was this Greek goddess, whose hair was described by Homer as golden.", "correct_answer": "Aphrodite", "incorrect_answers": ["Demeter", "Hera", "Medusa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lipitor and Zocor are two popular brand names which fall under what class of cholesterol lowering drugs?", "correct_answer": "Statins", "incorrect_answers": ["Citrates", "Hydrochlorides", "Aminoketones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All cats are born with green eyes.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who sings the song Tell Me Something I Don\u2019t Know in the movie Another Cinderella Story?", "correct_answer": "Mary", "incorrect_answers": ["Joey and Mary", "Joey", "Tami"]}]